Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records
1936-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union
5685
191.78 cubic feet
191.8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3121941
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 22, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5676: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5685 mf: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records on Microfilm 5685 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Photographs 5924: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Additional Records
Arrangement
Series I. HENRY FONER. PAPERS (Arranged alphabetically)
Sub-Series A. General Correspondence Sub-Series B - ORGANIZING DRIVES
Series II. MINUTES (Arranged in chronological order)
Sub-Series A. NYJB and Local Unions, 1937-1946 Sub-Series B. Executive Board, Membership meetings, elections and objection minutes for NY Joint Board & Local Unions, 1946-1949 Sub-Series C. NYJB & Local Unions Executive Board, Membership, Elections & Objections, Special, etc., meeting minutes, 1950-1957 Sub-Series D. Minutes of Executive, Membership Committee, Joint Administrative Committee & Board of Directors, 1956-1959 Sub-Series E. Minutes of Joint Board Locals, District #2, 1960
Series III - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1955-1956 Sub-Series B. LOCALS, 1956 Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1954-1957 Sub-Series B. LOCALS, 1957 Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1958 Sub-Series B. LOCALS, 1958-1959 Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1959 Sub-Series B. Locals, 1959 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1960 Sub-Series B. Locals, 1960 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1961 Sub-Series B. Locals, 1961 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1962 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1963 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1964 Sub-Series B. Locals, 1964 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1965 Sub-Series B. Locals, 1965 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1966 Sub-Series B. LOCALS, 1966 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1967 Sub-Series A. Joint Board, 1968 Sub-Series B. LOCALS, 1968 Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1969 Sub-Series A. JOINT BOARD, 1970 Sub-Series B. Locals, 1971
Series IV: District 2: Papers and Correspondence, 1940-1975
Series V: District 3 - Papers and Correspondence
Sub-Series A. Box 54, file 25 - Box 59 file 55, Organized by Local Union Sub-Series B. Box 60-Box 61 Folder 40: Joint Council 3 Agreements and Arbitration Sub-Series C. Box 61 Folder 41-Box 63: General Agreements/Records/Correspondence.
Series VI: Joint Council 3 - Papers & Correspondence
Series VII: Papers & Correspondence of Local Unions
Sub-Series Local 27, 1945-1971 Sub-Series Local 48, 1962-1969 Sub-Series Local 61, 1962 Sub-Series Local 64, 1958-1969 Sub-Series Local 88, 1962-1969 Sub-Series Local 150, 1962-1969 Sub-Series Local 206, Camden Leather Workers, 1949-1975
Series VIII: Welfare Department. Papers, 1940-1975
Sub-Series A. General, 1940-1968 Sub-Series B: United Mechanics, Local 150, 1968-1972 Sub-Series C: Sewing Machine Industry Insurance Fund, 1949-1967 Sub-Series D: Sewing Machine Industry Pension Fund Sheet, 1955-1969
Series IX: Disability Records, 1951-1976
Series X: Contracts, 1938-1970
Series XI: Miscellaneous Papers, 1949--1955
Series XII: Financial Records, 1939-1974
Sub-Series A. Joint Board Financial Records, 1939-1963 Sub-Series B. Joint Board Council Financial Records, 1944-1969 Sub-Series C. District's Financial Records, 1954-1970 Sub-Series D. Local's Financial Records, 1943-1974
Series XIII: Legal Files, 1955-1973
Sub-Series A. Legal Files - General, 1955-1958 Sub-Series Housing: See - next box, ff 1-7, 1964-1973 Sub-Series B. Realty Files
Series XIV: Printed Material
Sub-Series A. Organizing Campaign Materials Sub-Series B. Publications & other misc. documents
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Sources; Fur-workers -- Sources; Leather workers -- Labor unions -- Sources; Trade-unions. Leather workers. United States.; Joint Board of Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers' Union
3121941
- Series I. HENRY FONER. PAPERS (Arranged alphabetically)
  - Sub-Series A. General Correspondence
    - Allcraft Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Agreement between R-T-P Inc. and Community and Social Agency Employees Union, Local 107, District Council 1707, A.F.S.C.M.E., AFL-CIO; article by Joyce Hartley, which discusses how oppressive and unfairly society treats women; several letters praising the
    - Alpha Distributing Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Anti-Union letters to employees; letters from Cammer and Shapiro re: NLRB case; NLRB stipulation for certification upon consent election; correspondence between General Counsel, NLRB and Shapiro regarding employee fired from company; petition for re-certi
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters & Butchers Workmen (AMC&BW), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Letter to Harry Poole and Sam Talario re: inability to institute a dues increase to all locals; newsletters - topics include: how to deal with the ongoing Iowa Beef Strike; a legal memo making extraordinary employer discounts to union officials illegal; a
    - A.M.C.& B.W. Pension, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Routine
    - Amalgamated Press Association (Box 1, Folder 5)
      n.d. - By-Laws, Code of Ethics
    - AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - American Fur Industry Material on Constitution, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Minutes of Constitution Committee meeting, Constitution and By-Laws of the Fur Information and Fashion Council
    - American Fur Industry, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      History of fur legislation by Norman, Patterson and Farrell; memo to AFL Board of Directors from Leber, Katz Partner re: Annual Advertising Report; message from Mayor Koch stating that he does not support the fur industry necessity of leg traps because of
    - Bechroth, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Contracts
    - Bechroth Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      List of hourly job rates that are to be increased; letter from Paulia to Henry re: beginning Southwest Hides organizing drive
    - Borden Arbitration - Joseph Casey, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Brief of arbitration & decision
    - Borden Arbitration - Vernon Jenson, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Arbitration proceeding re: check off procedures & routine correspondence
    - Borden Arbitration - Pension Issue, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Brief re: the legalities of arbitrating No. 1554; memo re: pension plan amendment dispute with Ray Forrester, Arbitrator; opinion and award; and related documents
    - Borden Arbitration - Milton Rubin - Borden v. Durham, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Order to show cause for Durham overpayment case; petition to compel arbitration for Durham case; affirmation to arbitration hearing; correspondence
    - Borden Arbitration - Benjamin Wolf, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Letter from Benjamin Wolf to Jim Owen re termination and sick leave owed
    - Borden Contract Material, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
      1971 Contract Proposals; handwritten negotiation on contract; company proposals; new contract/memo of agreement
    - Bucilla, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Form letter to Bucilla workers encouraging them to sign authorization card; correspondence re the disciplinary acts taken against Michael Quasin; NLRB letter to Bucilla stating it was charged with violation of NLRA; organizers list of Greek Worker visits
    - Bucilla - Campaign, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Copy of the complaint & notice of hearing between Bucilla and F.L.M.J.B.A.M.C.&B.W. of NA; absenteeism policy changes; company propaganda; notices of pre-election; pamphlet entitled "Some Questions and Answers for Bucilla Workers"; notice of debate initia
    - Bucilla Material, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Authorization cards; interoffice correspondence from Bucilla management; letter from union thanking the workers for signing; notice to employees re new pension plan; essay entitled " Broken Promises, Injustices & Greed" by Michael Quash (a worker at Bucil
    - CABO ROJO, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Notice of Hearing between Fur Dressers & Dyers Division & Cabo Rojo Pessing Co.; demand and notice of intention
    - California Trapping Campaign, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Minutes from the California Rabies & Wildlife Council; anti-trap initiative (jawed traps); clipping from newspaper re: the jawed trap band; lithium chloride options; info on outlawing steel jaw traps and a petition for voters; general correspondence re me
    - Carabanchel 10 Trial, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      In Madrid 10 Spaniard's charged with organizing workers; article entitled "Spanish Rightist Disrupt Funeral of Slain Premier: - political demonstration during Premier Blanco's funeral; from Henry Foner to Morris Biller re meeting to hear a report on the t
    - Chesnut Operating Welfare Problems, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      General correspondence
    - Chile, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Proposed statement re: helping Chile's destroyed trade union movement from ILPA; letter addressed to H. Kissinger from Russel Gibbons re: the support Chilean trade unions need - by granting asylum to political refugees from Chile; NYTV Committee of Concer
    - Civil Rights Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Reports
    - Cosmopolitan Dry Cleaning, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      NLRB case, stipulation, order & correspondence; charge against U.M.L. 150, complaint & notice of hearing, stipulation & decision order; Cosmopolitan discriminating against 12 employees because they joined a union
    - Council of Jews for Racial Justice (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Information on council background, routine
    - Crown Monarch, 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 28A)
      2/8/71 Statement to the Int'l. Executive Board A.M.C.& B.W. of N.A. in behalf of Fur Dressers Union, Local 2-F, Fur Floor Workers Union, Local 3-F, & the J.B.F.L.M. Union re: wage differentials between Chicago & New York; to Foner from Local 2F/3F re Crow
    - Cutting Room Appliance Corp., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Retirement income plan for Cutting Room Appliance Corp.; Seely Employees Pension Plan; to Foner from Frederick J. Clark re: Henry Rand's retirement
    - District 21, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29A)
      Statement of H. Foner as co-chairman of District 21, Citizens for Community Control - includes 2 photos
    - East Side Story - Play from the book by Harold Farbstein with lyrics by H. Foner (Box 1, Folder 29B)
    - Endangered Species, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Copy of Public Law 91-135; an act to prevent the
    - Group Health Dental Insurance (GHDI), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
      Correspondence re the establishment of GHDI for the union; from Foner to George Melcher, President, GHDI, re: Melcher's bluff that the FLM Joint Board should insure GHDI against loss; other problems with GHDI also discussed; correspondence re: abbreviatin
    - Grove Press Arbitration (Box 1, Folder 33)
      From the Voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribune in the matter between FLMJB & Grove Press re: the discharges of employees for union activities; includes award of arbitrator; opinion, discussion of each employees case individually
    - Grove Press Election Material, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      April 1970 - information form the FLMJB encouraging Grove Press to vote for the union; bulletins; N.Y. Times "9 Women Arrested in 5-hour set-in at Grove Press" mentions Robin Morgan & WLM at Grove; Foner is going to request an election; denied connection
    - Illegal Aliens, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      H. Foner's witness opinion/testimony re: the problem/or media-induced problem of illegal immigration and the social/economic problems that they cause; Castillo (commissioner) to Posner (Chairman Assembly Committee) re: his opinion of hiring undocumented a
    - International Convention of Endangered Species, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      Draft positions for U.S. Position paper offered for public comment and discussion at Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora. 53 pp.
    - Labor Leadership - Assembly for Peace, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      Articles; Statement of Policy of the National Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace
    - Labor Leadership - Support Lindsey (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Handbills supporting the reelection of John V. Lindsay for Mayor of N.Y.C.
    - Liberals for McCarthy, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Lists of members of the liberal party; thank you letters for support; clippings; "McCarthy Pledges Creation of Jobs" & other articles dealing with the activities of McCarthy; correspondence re the support of Liberals for McCarthy
    - National Health Services, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Health perspectives deals with passage of National Health Services; copy of Senator Kennedy's paper re the role of private insurance companies in a comprehensive NHIP; a brochure explaining what the Health Service Action does how to join; list of union le
    - National Health Services - Health Service Action Memorabilia - button (Box 1, Folder 43)
      Correspondence re membership in the Health Service Action Line; educational activities in support of Health Services; clippings; packet of information for new Health Service Action members includes newsletters, clippings from periodicals; HSA meeting minu
    - National Issues Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Washington letter from the American Jewish Committee deals with affirmative action; letter from Philip J. Kaplan to Mr. Carl Grillo of the Liberal Party Headquarters re civil liberties H.R.686 in the criminal justice field and permissible scope of activit
    - Nelson, Steve Testimonial, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
      A dinner honoring the 39th anniversary of the struggle for a democratic Spain; photos; note re trip to the
    - New York Diabetes Association (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Letter to Mr. Alfred C. Nichols from H. Foner re organization of Camp NYDA and the creation of a parental committee
    - Newark Leather Division Elections, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      List of names and addresses of those in the Newark Leather Division; letter to superintendents re upcoming union elections; list of signatures of those who support the re-election of Joe McCoy; proposed election schedule for FLM Joint Board - Newark Leath
    - Newark YMCA, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
      Copy of personnel policy of Newark YMCA; contract proposals from FLM Joint Board, A.M.C.&B.W. of N.A.; handwritten copy of changes to contact retroactive to April 15; NLRB charge against Newark YMCA, failure to bargain; Joseph McCoy statement describing h
    - Ohio - Fur Trapping, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
      From Foner to Charles Monohan re an article he wrote entitled "Lines are Drawn on Trapping Ballot Issue" intended for publication in "Focus" an Ohio State AFL-CIO paper; financial statements; the Fouke case and the nursing of baby seals
    - Robeson, Paul Archives, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Tribute to Paul Robeson, an extraordinary individual who was "an athlete, a scholar, an actor & singer, & a champion of the rights of the common man"; program proposal, 1974-1975 for Paul Robeson Archives, a collection of Robeson's papers, records, tapes,
    - Shapson, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Notice of change of benefits for Shapson employees; memo of agreement and stipulation re severance pay; letter from Lewis Siegal of Cohn, Laiken, Sugel & Co. to Foner re: pension plan legal information
    - Shorter Work Week Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      An act to amend the length of work week and overtime pay introduced in NY State; financial report; memos re shorter work week; from Foner to Reisel re information about shorter work week bill and his article; from Foner to Frank Runnels, President of All
    - Shorter Work Week Conference, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      4/11/1978: Conference papers; keynote speech by Frank Runnels, President, agenda, resolutions, assembly bill, fact sheet
    - Shorter Work Week Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      "Background of the Struggle for a Shorter Work Week" by Henry Foner delivered on 10/25/77; speech by Frank Runnels, President of Steering Committee before All Unions Conference
    - South American Fur Co. - NLRB Case, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Articles; NLRB charge against several unions for picketing violations; NLRB vs. locals re picketing; NLRB (Sidney Danielson) vs. Fur Dressers; respondents' joint memorandum for dismissal of petition for signing Section 10 (1) inj.; Sidney Danielson vs. Fu
    - State Anti-Trapping Laws, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Letter to Foner from Buist re the Alaskan fur industry decline due to anti-trapping laws; correspondence re stopping the anti-trapping laws Assembly Bill 1293 & Senate Bill 213; letter of introduction for Dave Jenkins in California; Congressional report o
    - Trapping Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9-12)
      Correspondence re legislative bills dealing with the humane treatment of animals; facts for "pro" trapping; correspondence between Jess Cornice, Marius Scopton, Norman Wolfson and Bob Pyle on updates of legislation and what's being done to promote the "pr
    - Union, 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Financial records, statements
    - United States vs. Travis Paul Emmons, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      U.S. vs. Travis Paul Emmons, Jackie J. Bendo, Ed Wayne Barton & Milton Woodward; deals with whether violence during a lawful strike for higher wages & monetary benefits is really extortion; includes legal documents
  - Sub-Series B - ORGANIZING DRIVES
    Organizing records of various publishing houses
    - Authorization cards for the following employers (all that was in the folder) - Avon books, Crowell Collier Macmillan, Ballantine Books, E.P. Dutton, Harcourt, Brace & World, Litton Publishing, W.W. Norton & Co., Random House (Box 2, Folder 15)
      16
    - C.& P., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Organizing campaign flyers describing benefits, upcoming meetings, other successful drives for these leather workers
    - Goldsmith, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Local 27 - organizing campaign flyers describing other organized workers higher wages; benefits they may have; notices of special meeting/elections; in Spanish and English
    - Grove Press - Authorization Cards, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Grove Press, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 19-21)
      General Correspondence, newspaper clippings, legal papers; statements re the discharge of Martha Friedberg, Cicely Nichols, Robin Morgan Ditchfore, Bev. Ravitch for union activity; joint statement of Grove Press & FLMJB re discharge of employees & petitio
    - Grove Press Propaganda, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Essential facts you should know from Grove Press; reasons to vote against union; reasons to vote for FLM Joint Board; memo from several Grove Employees describing how it wants to set up an employee committee to deal with the problems at Grove and avoid an
    - Grove Press Workers, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
      Lists of workers who are pro-union/anti-union, etc.; status of contacts; addresses, etc., attendance sheets, copies of authorization cards
    - Harper & Row, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      To Jack Rich, Director of Personnel at Harper & Row re new program for workers (cost of living adj.); correspondence re the 8 pt. program that Foner proposed; from John Rich to H. Foner re response to the 8 pt. program (cost of living, min. hiring, etc.)
    - Harper & Row, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
      Preliminary Proposals for the new contract between Harper & Row employees and Harper & Row; list of proposed job classifications & minimum scales of pay; Rich to Foner re meeting to discuss contract proposals; Foner to Division of Employment re terminatio
    - McGraw Hill, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Authorization cards; to H. Foner from Paul Frost re receiving separation pay from McGraw-Hill; notice to support labor-student rally to stop them
    - Morse (Box 2, Folder 29)
      Handbill re Labor Board rejecting N.O.I.T.V. petition. Also in Spanish
    - Morse, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Publication from the FLM Joint Board entitled "We Support Our Union" pleas from those who support the union to other workers - the bigger the vote, the bigger the contract - In Spanish also; Propoganda to vote for FLMJB because it is legitimate not like N
    - Publishing Employees Organizing Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      Article from the New York Times entitled "In Publishing, the Word is Trouble" by Curt Shleier re costs, sales, labor problems in the industry; info from FLM to publishing employees answering questions about the union and how it works; flyers to encourage
    - Pyramid Publications, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      Authorization cards; list of employees for pyramid publications; list of conventional and drive-in theatres; list of eligible employees; Walter Reade organization newsletter; certification petition; letter to Pyramid Publications re FLM Board wanting to n
    - Schwarz, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      Union propaganda to Schwarz employees telling of benefits of joining Leather Workers Union in Spanish and English
    - Seton, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      Propaganda from Leather Workers Union, Local 27 to Seton employees describing benefits they can give; list of other companies they have organized; info from other members of Local 27 and what they have done for them
    - Tannery Topics, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      A newsletter published by Newark Leather Division in Spanish and English
    - W.W. Norton, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Authorization cards, personnel directory
    - Waljon, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Leather Worker's Union, Local 27 Propoganda describing benefits union could give in Spanish and English
- Series II. MINUTES (Arranged in chronological order)
  - Bound volume, Local 37 of the Pennsylvania & New Jersey Leather Locals, 1938-1942 (Box 3, Folder All)
    1/20/38 - 4/8/42
  - Sub-Series A. NYJB and Local Unions, 1937-1946
    Including 2 volumes of Local 206 of New Jersey Locals; Includes Executive Board, membership, elections & objections, special meeting minutes
    - Local 88, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Local 88, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Local 64, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      5/38-12/38
    - Local 80, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      6/38-12/38
    - Local 88, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Local 88, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Local 64, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Local 64, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Local 80, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Local 80, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Local 88, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Local 88, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Local 64, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Local 64, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Local 80, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Local 88, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Local 88, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Local 206, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      2/9-8/21
    - Local 64, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Local 64, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Local 80, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      January-June
    - Local 88, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Local 206, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 22A)
      Executive Meetings
    - Local 64, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Local 64, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Local 206, 1943-1946 (Box 4, Folder 25)